<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Paul Strickland</title>
    <link>https://pestrickland.co.uk/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Paul Strickland</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2018 12:21:57 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://pestrickland.co.uk/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Good Day</title>
      <link>https://pestrickland.co.uk/posts/good-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Aug 2018 21:16:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pestrickland.co.uk/posts/good-day/</guid>
      <description>Today was a good day. Perhaps even a very good day. A great day? Maybe that&amp;rsquo;s going too far, but it was good enough to make me think about why I left the office feeling that I&amp;rsquo;d accomplished a lot.
A little bit about my job I work in an office with a team of eight people. I should actually clarify that by saying that I lead the team, but I don&amp;rsquo;t like to sound self-important.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The ErgoDox keyboard</title>
      <link>https://pestrickland.co.uk/posts/ergodox/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pestrickland.co.uk/posts/ergodox/</guid>
      <description>I built an ErgoDox keyboard in 2013 from a kit sold by MassDrop. It was designed as a split ergonomic keyboard that is highly customisable. There&amp;rsquo;s a lot written about it on the internet that I can&amp;rsquo;t usefully add to, but these two posts were particularly useful to me:
 The ErgoDox keyboard a year in, and why you should get one Oh (Ergonomic) Keyboard, Where Art Thou? (archive)  After spending a weekend building the keyboard and a few weeks learning how to program it and trying to type on it, it spent a long time being neglected.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Splashing out</title>
      <link>https://pestrickland.co.uk/posts/londinium/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pestrickland.co.uk/posts/londinium/</guid>
      <description>The last year has been an exciting one for me as I discovered speciality coffee. After starting off with a variety of ground coffee, I quickly discovered the benefit of freshly grinding beans. Before too long I&amp;rsquo;d purchased a Gaggia Classic to make espresso. This then led to a new grinder to produce good espresso without having to spend ages using a hand grinder.
Throughout 2015 my quest for exceptional espresso continued.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coffee Update</title>
      <link>https://pestrickland.co.uk/posts/coffee_update/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pestrickland.co.uk/posts/coffee_update/</guid>
      <description>Over the past four months I&amp;rsquo;ve ventured into the world of coffee and have quickly been drawn into it. Although I started with a simple French Press and stove-top moka pot, I progressed into owning two grinders and an espresso machine. And for the last two months or so I&amp;rsquo;ve been drinking espresso almost exclusively.
After a lot of practice I&amp;rsquo;m now in a position where I can make what I consider an acceptable espresso.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Elephant from Guatemala and a Tiny Italian</title>
      <link>https://pestrickland.co.uk/posts/elephant/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pestrickland.co.uk/posts/elephant/</guid>
      <description>Guatemalan Elephant As my exploration of coffee continued, I tried a bag of Guatemala Elephant coffee from Whittard. The beans that went into the grinder were huge, presumably leading to the elephant in the name.
I made this in a stove-top pot, and when it was brewed I was amazed at the dark, almost thick liquid that poured into my cup. Had I tried this earlier in my introduction to coffee I&amp;rsquo;d probably have grimaced at the potent taste.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coffee</title>
      <link>https://pestrickland.co.uk/posts/coffee/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pestrickland.co.uk/posts/coffee/</guid>
      <description>For as long as I can remember, I&amp;rsquo;ve been a tea drinker. Although coffee had an appeal due to its smell, not to mention (to my inner geek/engineer) the appeal of so many different contraptions used to make it, I never learned to like its taste. And that became the status quo for me until only a few weeks ago. So why did I suddenly try drinking grown-up coffee?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>